He has not come to see it, he too will come, come,
loot guys welcome back with new video and today
we have to get a haircut at our very favourite Nadi Mai's salon, we are
going out now, so bye bye it is done,
so this is our Hayabusa which is
ready in a very wonderful way today,
it has been prepared after millions of years and has been
polished very much, so today we are
going to show you some drums, that too
with mummy
[music]
and you can see we are in Sironj right now
and the powder has been decorated so nicely
and the crackers are also bursting very loudly, ah
and now we are going to pick up mummy
because we have to go with mummy, come
out to
9th, let's go quickly and
meet you at mummy's place, so we have reached
Sector-6 and
will pick up mummy here and we will go
quickly, we have to go
with mom to see a beautiful scenery, ah so
hello brother, this our mummy is
sitting in the back of our car and  We are moving ahead, so let me
reveal it right now, we are going to the
Municipal Corporation of NM C because it is
decorated very nicely and beautifully,
I want to show it there and there is also a wedding here
which is decorated very nicely,
it is very beautifully,
we are going there,
now we will reach there immediately and after showing it to Amma, we will leave, let's meet on the
9th, should we have
meat, is it meat, right,
people check a lot there, right now
where I am going, let's
show you something in a good way, it will go through the
highway, burn from here, from inside,
yes, so we will catch it, right now the highway is
and everyone is roaming around,
what is Hindu Muslim in it, are you an
Indian, so yes one more thing, I
forgot to say Happy Diwali to everyone, Happy 222 and
Maths Fiber and those who have not subscribed
and are watching the video, then
please subscribe, thank you for subscribing to the
channel, so right now we are at Palm Beach and we are moving
there and that means point today means if there was an
operation, then I would have seen something like this in lemon  A
lot has
happened
that today all the couples will meet in this, you guys will find
one Hari Amit sitting in the back, I am Muslim, I
rarely go out with my mother, I mean I
always stay with her, if I travel somewhere long
or if I have to go somewhere, I rarely go out
with her,
but we want to spend those moments with our mother
because this is the time, those moments
because time is there, once the time is gone,
then it never comes back, our
belief is that
you enjoy with your mother, family, enjoy with everyone
and spend crores of time, our
today's knowledge is for you guys,
so we will meet you quickly there, so guys, West
Indies is coming, you are
seeing our embassy, ​​this is what I
remembered to show you and to show our subscribe bus
how cheap your New Mumbai is,
so we are going to go here now, soon,
ah,
many people come here,
ah, New Mumbai Police always cooperates with all of you, no matter
how many people are there, so right now I will also go and
show my mother to me
and will my mother get something done
or you can also go  If we go, many people
come here for photo shoots, you
can see here, you guys call
Ajay, you
cannot go inside, now you can stay outside, if it is with
Ajay then this is
sitting, so
hello Gayatri, Har Jeet and Mummy,
call your brother, Nibha,
I am talking to my brother on video call
and I will show you, it looks very
bad,
Kar Do
[Music]
Jhal
Kar Do
[Music]
Loot Lo
Kar Do Kar
Do
[Music]
so guys it looks very nice, if you can see it from the front then if you
see something normal then you will be surprised, it looks
beautiful, but this Diwali
in Dubai, you guys finished, friends, it will be
closed from tomorrow, close the settings in the last,
and Mummy is telling her brother on video call
how did you like it, it looks
very nice, it
looks very nice, you don't want to see that by the time
you guys come, everything will be removed,
today from here till Diwali is over
and this is my Hayabusa which always worked
for a day,
Ajay, so this is to
show this  We had
brought Mummy after travelling from such a far distance and we
also wanted to see her happy and we had to make you do something,
then I think but two bikes, we will
enjoy now and see, she is
in this very nighty, look, tell me more, tell me
Ajay has to be in the
hospital,
so guys, right now we will enjoy with his view, this is it
and finish our blog, a few like it is, I
mean, from the camera's point of view, you might
not be able to see her, how beautiful
and how jointed she is, but if you come like this, then it is
very big, but anyone
can come near her, you guys, now on this day, that day
too, we will come, Insha Allah, it looks very beautiful,
if you liked the video, then like,
subscribe and share, right now we are in the video,
love you, enjoy and then we say goodbye,
bye-bye, see you
in the next video.